Stúdió 1 presents
BINDING SENTIMENTS
Starring MARI TÖRŐCSIK
Cast
Screenplay by MÁRTA MÉSZÁROS
Script editor: YVETTE BÍRÓ
Music by LEVENTE SZÖRÉNYI
Lyrics by JÁNOS BRÓDI
Director of photography: JÁNOS KENDE
Directed by MÁRTA MÉSZÁROS
dr. TIBOR BALASSA
1922-1967
- Good day.
- Welcome.
- Hi.
Dear comrades,
We have suffered a heavy loss.
By a sudden and tragic misfortune,
senseless death has robbed
us of our young, talented
and highly esteemed
comrade Tibor Balassa.
He was one of those
whose life and activity
nothing can make up for.
He was an extraordinary man.
A talented researcher,
an excellent economist,
who knew no obstacles.
When he started to do something,
he fulfilled his task,
whatever obstacles he found
standing in his way.
His friends,
acquaintances, colleagues loved
him and held him in high esteem.
Comrades,
with deep sorrow in our hearts,
we now pay our last respects to him.
The sorrow we feel...
cannot be expressed by words.
Let us pay tribute to his memory
with silence.
Go on a journey, try to find peace.
I'll help you in whatever I can.
I must go now... but I'll contact you.
- Bye.
Dark night...
Who could chase it away if...
Who could chase it away if it was...
Who could chase it away
if it was approaching me?
And the girl would do what needs
to be done if I asked her.
- Pale moonlight...
- Well?
- Do you want to go with your granny?
- Yes.
You can stay for a week.
I will call your head teacher
and tell him.
Thanks.
István was here, but didn't want to
come in. He said he would be back later.
When I finally let her go...
Doesn't this music disturb you?
I've got used to it.
Does it irritate you?
Thank you.
Well...
I'll see you in a week. Bye.
You'll go without me, granny?
Of course, you can go, my son.
Bye.
- I'll go now.
- Bye.
- Take care of yourself.
- Okay.
Bye.
Hello, mother.
Did you not want to let me in?
Hello.
I knew you had a key.
I read in the papers
about father's death.
I've been waiting for you to call me.
But you didn't.
So here I am.
I would have called you.
I'm glad you're back.
Good morning, Mancika.
Good morning.
I'm so sorry, but I was very tired.
- I thought you were still asleep.
- Never mind.
What's the time?
I don't know, but it's rather late.
I'm done with everything.
I got up late.
I thought I shouldn't come.
I tried to phone, but nobody answered.
So I came.
The flat must be cleaned up anyway.
You did the right thing.
I'm sorry. I'll be off at once.
I'll bring some coffee.
Who would dare deny
that we need this light?
To see her face
when I finally let her go.
Thank you.
There was barely any green grass
in the square
A cigarette?
Thank you.
I caught a cold there, I think
I woke up in the early morning
I hit the road in the morning fog
Another night has passed
Remember, Editke?
In '56...
you stood there at the kitchen door
when I came and said...
"My husband has fled the country."
It's like he died, too.
Even worse...
Why it happened this way, I don't know.
It smells good.
It smells rich.
What I had to do with girls.
I don't remember my husband anymore.
I often take out
his photograph and look at it.
I can't remember his face.
Nobody had come to my place
You want to cry, don't you?
But you can't.
I can't.
But if I found her one day
The one I'm always waiting for
I wouldn't believe it's her, I think
Good afternoon.
Hello.
Lenin: the new economic policy
and popular education committees.
Page 47.
"The new economic policy means"
that we replace compulsory
deliveries with taxation
"to restore capitalism to
a considerable extent."
Engels: On the history of criticism
Page 225.
"Concerning this misunderstanding,
what Hume really..."
When I was a child, I would always
sit here and watch him work.
I haven't been allowed to
enter for 2 years.
Nor have I. Except to bring him
his breakfast and coffee.
You kept arguing for ten years.
I think both of you were guilty.
Do you still live with that girl?
Yes.
We're together.
You didn't let her come to see me here.
I know that's why you moved out.
If you don't mind, I'd
like to bring her here now.
Are you going to marry her?
No, not yet.
Is this the only way you can think of?
She's still studying and so am I.
Did you ever go to university?
For three years...
but then I quit.
Is this a bad time?
No.
Kati is here. May she come in?
All right.
Kati, come in.
How do you do?
Hello.
Sit down.
Shall I make a coffee?
I'm taking sedatives,
I don't drink any coffee.
No coffee for me either.
Mother, Kati has moved in with us.
I have noticed.
But if you don't agree,
we can both leave.
I wish you did not set
any conditions, son.
You can both stay.
The flat and everything
that goes with it is yours.
I've got nothing to do
with anything here.
That's how you and father always talked.
That's yours, that's mine,
you did it, I did it.
- I don't like you talking like that.
- I don't feel like arguing now.
I've had enough.
She knows everything.
You can talk freely.
I'm tired. Leave me alone.
We'll talk later.
Very well.
- Good-bye.
- Bye.
- Hello.
- Good evening.
Go inside.
- Please.
- Hello.
This way.
Come inside.
Good evening.
Go inside, please.
What is this?
I've gathered Tibor's friends...
and colleagues.
I wanted to see them all together.
Who... is that Grey-haired man?
The new deputy minister.
- And that guy is the old one.
- I know him.
- Is that Gyuri?
- What about him?
Nothing. I think he's a chemist.
Excuse me.
Hello.
- Good evening.
My condolences.
It came so unexpectedly.
I read it in the papers.
How are you, Gyuri?
Thanks.
I've been working a lot.
I'm bringing up my sons.
What do you do these days?
I'm an engineer.
Have you left politics?
I'm an engineer...
and very fond of my job.
Why did you make them all come?
Do you like them?
Not all of them.
Some of them.
You didn't like Tibor either.
But only since '49.
He always pretended as if
nothing had happened.
Though he knew lots of things had.
He was going to be a great economist,
but he became a party functionary.
Excuse me, I must leave you now.
You intend to go and ask everybody
about their opinion on Tibor?
What is this?
A test?
Or just hysterics?
They regarded him as a great man.
Are you sure?
I am.
And you?
All right, I won't keep you. Go ahead.
If you talk like that,
I'll send you away.
You wouldn't dare.
There are too many people here...
and you have always been
afraid of scandals.
I can't believe it!
I've been on sedatives for days.
I really don't know what to say now.
- Please.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I heard the news in Rome,
at the Embassy.
Your children, your pension, all good?
Yes, thank you.
Come and see me one evening,
I'd like to talk to you.
All right, I will.
Ring me up next week,
- I'm always in by about 8 o'clock.
- All right.
I'm sorry, but I must be going now.
I'll take a French leave.
Wait a moment.
I asked you to come...
because I wanted...
all of Tibor's friends to be together...
and meet each other.
I want...
all of you to take a book
from his library.
Whichever you like.
Please.
Help yourselves.
Come...
Come and choose.
Come.
Mother, what's this?
Mind your own business.
You must be very tired.
Don't worry. I won't hurt his memory.
I'm worried for you.
Calm down.
- Good-bye.
Good-bye.
Good night.
- Bye
- Bye.
Good-bye.
- Good-bye.
Bye. I took this one.
- Give me a call.
- All right.
Calm down, try to have some rest.
Bye.
Do you mind if I call you Edit again?
I want to talk to you and
being formal bothers me.
All right.
How are you doing without me?
I haven't seen you in 15 years.
That's not true.
It was just a week ago.
Don't be foolish.
It's been 15 years.
I've forgotten you.
That's true.
Because you've only ever
thought of yourself.
Actually...
only the first three years...
- of the last twenty were good.
- No, that's not true.
You've asked them to come
because you wanted their advice?
Because you never loved me.
You were just afraid of me.
You have been left alone
- and are embarrassed.
- No!
Don't do that.
You have no right to.
You've staged this little play.
The beautiful, sad...
and honest widow...
who's having a fit of conscience.
You wanted to live well.
In comfort.
In peace.
But you never achieved peace...
because you're restless inside...
I can't feel sorry for you.
I just wish you enough strength...
to play the game to the end.
Wait.
That's István, my son. Present yourself.
Don't you remember me?
No, I don't.
I was a friend of your father's.
István...
Tell him why you left home.
That you didn't get along
with your father.
Because you were always fighting.
Tell him!
Mother, calm down. This concerns
only the two of us.
I don't want to bother you.
I'll get going now.
Bye.
- Bye.
- Good-bye.
You're tired.
- You'd better go to bed.
- No.
It suits you well.
I like these very much, I just
don't know where to wear them.
- This one's not bad either.
- Don't you have anything in my size?
There are a lot over there.
There.
I have a white coat.
I bought it in Paris. Here.
Too big for me.
It should be okay for you.
I'll try it on.
- What a fine textile!
- It's wonderful!
Look at these colours!
Which shoes should I wear with this?
It's your size, isn't it?
- Keep it.
- Not bad.
I don't want any of them.
These are not my style.
Silk!
I have a pile of sweaters there.
I can't accept them.
Then I'll throw them out.
Oh, how lovely!
It looks so good on you!
You think so?
Sweet Jesus, but where will I wear it?
- This one's Dior, right?
- Yes.
Marvellous!
Oh dear!
All these beautiful clothes!
And the bag?
Come in.
- Good day.
- Hello.
- Sit down.
My hat, you fool!
Want some whisky?
Yes, please.
Won't Kati come in?
What's going on here?
Edit gave us her clothes.
I'd like you to leave us alone.
I'll go and see you when I'm finished.
I want to talk to you.
I want to talk to you here and now.
Does that mean you want us to leave?
Yes.
That's nice...
- Bye, my dear Edit.
- Bye.
- So long and thanks.
- Good-bye.
- Bye.
And now, leave me alone. At once!
I want to talk to you now.
Sit down. I'm almost done.
- Good afternoon.
- Hello.
I'm listening, mother.
I made up my mind not to accept
the 200 000 forint insurance
and the pension.
I'll let you have it.
As well as the flat.
I'm going to the ministry
to sign it today.
I want you to come with me.
I won't go.
I've thought it over thoroughly.
You have?
I don't think so.
I have nothing to do
with anything here.
Neither the money nor the flat.
Your father worked for all of this.
- And you lived with him for 21 years.
- That's true.
But we had nothing in common.
Except that he cared for me
and we didn't get a divorce.
He was the one who was against it.
That's your business, mother.
But you have to see this through.
For the sake of my father's memory.
For once I'll really
see something through.
I won't go with you.
If you've kept silent until now, you
can go on keeping silent and endure.
You won't give up anything,
I won't let you.
Calm down.
Otherwise you're free
and can live as you wish.
That's what father always said:
"You won't get a divorce
and you can live as you wish."
I don't mean to offend you, but
I can't take your decision seriously.
If you weren't strong enough before,
how could you could live on
1200 forints in a rented room now?
You have no trade.
I don't think you could do it.
Concerning the ethical part,
I won't let you hurt father.
Because, unlike you, I loved him.
- You don't understand me.
- No, I don't.
- Please, come with me.
- No, I won't.
Then I'll see to it myself.
Kati, come on, let's go.
Quick.
All right, tell her to come.
Mother, please...
would you come out?
Good evening.
- Hello.
- Kati's made supper for us.
She's a very good cook.
Let's make up, mother.
Okay.
Cheers.
Believe me, I love you
and I understand you.
But now you're nervous.
This, too, I understand.
You should go to the bungalow
for a week and get some rest.
I can't go now.
I have work to do.
A little rest could really do you good.
Kati will go with you...
- and care for you.
- Oh yes.
I've got things to arrange here.
I can't go now nor do I want to go.
All right. Then stay.
You do what you want.
Here's to you!
I'm sorry, but you have to go now.
I had no idea you'd come.
We ended up coming.
- Are you going to stay for long?
- I don't know yet.
Never mind.
Come on, girls!
But I hope you don't feel cross, do you?
- Well... be good and bye.
- Bye.
Bye and thanks!
- Thanks for everything. Bye!
- Bye!
Good morning.
Just call me and I'll open it.
How did I get here?
We brought you here last night.
István drove, but he went back.
I'm here to care for you.
You need to rest.
I can't remember anything.
We put sleeping pills in your wine.
Clever methods.
Cleverly done.
What would you like to have
for breakfast?
Coffee?
Eggs?
Milk?
We'll stay for a week.
You're mistaken.
There's a bus leaving
at 11 from the village.
I'll take the afternoon
train to Budapest.
- You can't do that.
- I'll do it.
I'm pretty strong.
All the doors are locked.
I'll follow you everywhere.
So I'll have to escape.
Very funny.
You can't escape.
Here's your breakfast.
Why are you doing this?
István asked me.
Do you love him?
Yes.
Will you marry him?
I will, if he proposes to me.
I'll get dressed.
Come here.
Come.
Hello, Cili.
Is Cili her name?
Yes.
What would you like to have for lunch?
Thanks for the excellent waiting,
but like I said,
I'm taking the 11 o'clock home.
You'd better not or
I'll have to lock you in.
- Would you do it?
- I would.
So you would lock me in.
All right.
Since we're going to spend
a week together,
we could make up the
programme together.
- I want you to have a good time.
- Who do you think you are?
Do you think I'm afraid of you?
Who are you?
And what have you got to do with me?
I'm Kati Csák, I'm a chemist student.
I was born in '45 in Dorog.
I don't think much of myself, but...
I think you're afraid of me...
because you're afraid of your son, too.
It's not true.
I'm not afraid of him.
You are.
Cili!
That's it. Come here.
Good.
I hope now you know...
that I can leave if I want to.
Cili!
Cili dear!
Good morning.
I feed her.
We live here next door.
Who are you?
Kati, István's fiancée.
We are here with his mother,
she's resting.
Oh yes, I hear the gentleman died.
- How is Edit?
- She's asleep now. She's exhausted.
I have a favour to ask you.
Could you feed the dog
for one more day?
Why not?
- Let her out.
- Thank you.
Cili! Good-bye.
- See you later.
- Thank you so much.
Good-bye.
The dog?
With the neighbours.
Very tricky.
- The gate?
- I've locked it.
You'd even beat me if you had to.
No, I'll just lock you up.
Try to rest and don't be hysterical.
Cili!
Come here, Cili!
- Cili!
- Come, Cili, come!
- Is she your dog?
- No, my mother's.
Come on, Cili.
How clever is she?
- Fetch it!
- Come, doggy!
We're going to have a bath.
Jump, Cili!
- Cili! Come back.
- Show us how clever you are, Cili.
Cili... jump!
- She won't obey you.
- Cili, jump! Hop!
She made it.
Hop! Come on now.
- Hello.
- Hi.
What's up?
We almost had a fight.
She wants to leave by all means.
I think we should stop doing this.
Just carry on.
Shouldn't we let her go?
We have to carry on just for some days.
I know my mother.
She's hysterical.
But it will soon be over.
I don't think so.
- Gáspár, bring that girl in here!
- Give it to me for a sec.
Oh my, it's cold! But it's fine.
It's forbidden to swim here!
Come out and show me your papers!
Come out!
Hurry up!
What are you doing here?
- Is it forbidden to swim here?
- We're playing chess.
Come on, hurry up!
Come out!
The dog doesn't like it either.
Get dressed, quick!
Hurry up.
You, too.
- Give me my shoes.
- Hurry up.
- You! Put on your gown.
- Me?
Come on.
You look lovely.
Look out! You're treading on my shirt!
- Where are you staying?
- At the camping.
Why? What's wrong?
I know what his problem is.
We have long hair,
we're hooligans, aren't we?
Come on, put it on.
You'd better behave.
- We did behave, we just went bathing.
- I know.
- Get going.
- Hi.
- I didn't know you were here.
- Take your clothes.
He's my brother.
Get going.
- Come on, Gáspár.
- No, I'm going with them.
Take that, too.
- Let's go to the police station.
- Where are my shoes?
Gáspár, come back!
Come on, Cili!
- Stop turning back, go ahead!
- All right.
- Let's go!
- Why do we have to go?
You'll find out at the station.
- You want to tell me how to breathe, too?
- We are pioneers!
Lunch is ready.
Won't you eat?
I'm sorry.
Say, can you be hired to do anything?
You want my son, you can have him.
Not only do I want him...
but he also wants me.
Edit dear!
How are you, aunt Margit?
Already awake?
Yes.
Good day.
I was told your husband died.
Let him rest in peace.
And how are you, dear?
Thanks... I am OK.
Kati's got the key.
Kati!
Open up!
Good day.
My son's fiancée.
We've met already.
When are you going to get married?
In a year, when I've
finished university.
My husband, too, died 10 years ago.
He was a good man and a good farmer.
I was left alone with nine children.
- Do sit down, aunt Margit.
- Thank you.
Is she a decent girl?
Oh yes, very decent.
All right, then.
Well... I'll be going now,
I'm very busy.
Wait, aunt Margit.
I'll go with you.
I'll take a walk.
Don't go, please.
Wash the dishes.
I'll be back soon. Bye.
Good-bye.
I'm so glad you came.
Two of my daughters
will come from Budapest.
We stick together.
My four sons also often come to see me.
- We're rather attached to each other.
- And to money.
And to money as well.
What would you have done with
the children parted from your husband?
- We gave you a home.
- Yes, indeed.
But I work like a horse.
- Have some wine, Edit, it's really good.
- Thank you.
I wanted to study,
but I wasn't accepted by the school.
My husband is a locksmith.
He's a drunkard, he'd beat me up,
so I left him.
Why aren't you studying now?
How could we manage if I studied?
Mother will find me
a vintner for a husband.
- Won't you, mother?
- Of course I will.
Have a drink, it's very good.
She's left with aunt Margit.
- We should stop this whole business.
- No.
She won't leave anyway.
Walk over to aunt Margit's,
I'll come by later.
Okay.
Come in.
And do you love me?
I do.
I think.
Have some more.
You must be very sad now.
Why are you sad?
Her husband died. A week ago.
Did you love him?
She did.
He was a big man up in Budapest.
If you loved him, drink.
The same if you didn't.
Stars up in the heavens
Gleam and glow and glisten!
Show the poor lad the way
For he can't find his lover's house
It's a beautiful lady I'm wooing
To the ugly ones, I pay no attention
Oh my heart, no one should know
That I love that blonde girl
Only the gypsy playing the violin
knows it
Edit, what's your song?
"A road so wide..."
A road so wide, a road so long
My angel set off on
My angel, come back
from your long journey
Remember your broken promise
We cannot come back
from too long a journey
There’s no concealing love
The love I feel is
bigger than the sea
I am lonelier than a dead leaf
- Hello, my son.
- Good day to you.
This is my vintner.
- Good day, aunt Margit.
- Good day.
Have some goulash, Edit,
it's really good.
I knew you'd come after me.
Go on, have a drink.
Don't drink any more.
Let's go home.
I'm going back to Budapest today.
You're drunk. Come home
and get some sleep.
So what! I'm drunk.
Don't drink any more.
Don't drink.
I won't go, leave me alone.
Have a drink, you're so insipid.
I won't go anywhere!
I'll go home! I'll do what I want to.
- Help me, will you? Let's take Edit home.
- Okay.
Where?
Where are you taking her?
Don't take her away!
- Let's go, shall we?
- No.
- Let's go.
Let's not make a scene.
I won't go.
Why won't you leave me alone?
Margit, help me.
Don't let her take me away.
- Calm down, Edit dear.
- No.
Your sorrow will soon be over.
Please, don't let her take me away!
You'll get some sleep
and it will pass.
- Leave me alone. I don't want to.
- Come with us.
- Please, leave me alone.
- Let's go.
I found this.
Come and have a drink.
Don't drink.
Come on.
Okay.
Come on and drink.
You're quite a decent gendarme.
No...
you aren't so decent after all.
You think I'm a coward.
Well... that's what I am.
I put up with my husband,
I didn't get a divorce,
I didn't have the guts to do it.
But...
at least I know...
I do know what I am like.
But you think what
you're doing to me...
is somehow different.
You just want to marry...
István,
because you slept with him.
Because he's clever...
and handsome.
But I know...
that my son is just like his father was.
Please... don't drink any more.
Leave me alone!
Go! Leave me alone!
I'll go and leave you alone,
but first I want to tell you something.
You said I was a gendarme and insipid.
And I'm doing this, because I understand
none of what happened to you.
And because I slept with your son.
Well, maybe I am insipid indeed
and have no sense
of sophisticated things,
nevertheless, I do know
myself and I know you.
You're absolutely a coward,
you've never taken any risks.
There's nothing wrong with
having a fine flat and a villa.
I would like that, too.
Why do you say that everybody
respected your husband?
You know this hasn't
been true for a long time.
People considered him selfish, vain...
and conservative.
You knew it, still you endured,
what's worse, you served him.
And now if you want to play
the honourable widow's role,
I'll let you go.
This playing the gendarme thing
was really stupid of me.
You do what you want.
Besides... you're right.
Your son is handsome and clever.
That's why I loved him.
But now I'll go.
Kati!
Kati! Stop!
I want to talk to you!
Kati!
Why are you leaving?
- Stay here.
- No.
I'm going.
Stay here.
I need you.
I love you.
You don't need me.
I've told you, I won't do it.
Do it alone.
- Did you think it through?
- I did.
Stay here.
Stay here... understand?
I want you to stay, I demand it!
I've already told you,
I won't stay. I'm going.
Hello, Gáspár!
What are you doing here?
Nothing. Just killing
time with the girls.
You've left them?
Yes. I'm going back to Budapest.
Well, bye, then.
I'll stay for a while.
Okay. Bye.
She's wearing a white sweater.
She's not mourning.
What's in your bag?
Leave that girl alone!
Let me court her!
Leave her alone!
Stop that monkey business!
Let her go!
We bid you farewell.
Bye!
Hey! Look who's there!
Chain, chain, turning chain,
Thread of the turning chain,
Would it be a thread...
Who would dare deny that we need...
Who would dare deny that
we need this light?
To see her face
when I finally let her go.
THE END
Stúdió1礼物
结合感
由MARITÖRŐCSIK主演
投
MÁRTAMÉSZÁROS的剧本脚本编辑：YVETTEBÍRÓ
LEVENTESZÖRÉNYIL的音乐JÁNOSBRÓDI的歌词
摄影总监：JÁNOSKENDE
由MÁRTAMÉSZÁROS执导
TIBOR BALASSA1922-1967博士
-美好的一天-美好的一天
-欢迎-嗨
亲爱的同志们，
我们蒙受了沉重的损失
由于突然而悲惨的不幸，
无知的死亡夺走了我们年轻而有才华的力量
蒂博尔·巴拉萨（Tibor Balassa）同志
他是其中之一
他们的生活和活动无法弥补
他是一个非凡的人
才华横溢的研究者，杰出的经济学家，
没有障碍的人
当他开始做某事时，
他完成了他的任务，
他遇到的任何障碍
他的朋友们，
熟人，同事们都爱他，并高度敬重他
同志们
内心深处的悲伤，我们现在向他表示最后的敬意
我们感到悲伤
不能用言语表达
让我们默默地悼念他
继续前进，努力寻找和平
我会尽力帮助您
我现在必须走了，但我会联系你的
- 再见
黑夜
如果谁能将它赶走
如果是的话，谁能把它赶走
如果它接近我，谁能追赶它呢？
如果我问她，那个女孩会做什么。
-苍白的月光-好吗？
-你想和奶奶一起去吗？-是的
你可以住一个星期
我会打电话给你的班主任
告诉他
谢谢
伊斯万（István）在这里，但不想进来。他说他稍后会回来
当我终于放开她
这音乐不打扰您吗？
我已经习惯了，这会激怒您吗？
谢谢
好吧
我待会再见
你会没有我的，奶奶？
我儿子当然可以走了
再见
-我现在去-再见
-照顾好自己-好吧
再见
你好母亲
你不想让我进去吗？
你好
我知道你有一把钥匙
我读过有关父亲去世的论文
我一直在等你给我打电话
但是你没有
所以我在这里
我会打电话给你
我很高兴你回来了
早上好，曼奇卡
早上好
我很抱歉，但是我很累
-我以为你还在睡觉-没关系
几点了？
我不知道，但是已经很晚了
我起得晚
我以为我不该来
我试图打电话，但是没人接
所以我来了
无论如何都必须清理公寓
你做了件对的事
对不起，我马上下车
我带杯咖啡
谁敢否认我们需要这种光？
当我终于放开她时去看她的脸
谢谢
广场上几乎没有绿草
香烟？
谢谢
我想我在那里感冒了
我一大早就醒了
我在晨雾中上路
又一个夜晚过去了
还记得吗，Editke？
在'56
我来的时候你站在厨房的门口
“我丈夫逃离了国家”
好像他也死了
甚至更糟
为什么这样发生，我不知道
闻起来很香
我跟女孩子有什么关系
我不记得我丈夫了
我经常拍张照片看看
我不记得他的脸
没有人来我家
你想哭，不是吗？但是你不能
我不能
但是如果我有一天找到她
我一直在等待的那个
我不相信是她
下午好
你好
列宁：新经济政策和大众教育委员会
第47页
“新的经济政策手段”
我们用税收代替了强制性的交付
“在很大程度上恢复资本主义”
恩格斯：论批评的历史
第225页
“关于这种误解，
休ume到底是什么
当我还是个孩子的时候，我会一直坐在这里看着他的工作
我已经两年没被允许进入
除了带早餐和咖啡外，我也没有
你吵了十年
我觉得你们两个都有罪
你还和那个女孩住在一起吗？
是的
我们在一起
你没有让她来这里见我
我知道那就是你搬出去的原因
如果您不介意，我想现在把她带到这里
你要嫁给她吗？
还没有
这是您唯一能想到的方法吗？
她还在读书，我也是
你上过大学吗？
三年来
但后来我辞职了
这是不好的时光吗？
不
卡蒂在这里，她可以进来吗？
好的
卡蒂，进来
你好吗？
你好
坐下
我可以煮咖啡吗？
我正在服用镇静剂，我不喝咖啡
我也不喝咖啡
妈妈卡蒂（Kati）和我们一起住了
我注意到了
但是，如果您不同意，我们都可以离开
我希望你没有任何条件，儿子
你们俩都可以留下
公寓以及与之相关的一切都是您的
我这里没事
那是你和父亲经常说话的方式
那是你的，那是我的，你做到了，我做到了
-我不喜欢你这样说话-我现在不想吵架
我受够了
她什么都知道你可以畅所欲言
我累了让我一个人呆
我们以后再说
很好
- 再见拜拜
- 你好你好
-晚上好-晚上好
进去
-请-您好
这条路
请你进来
晚上好
请进去
这是什么？
我聚集了蒂博尔的朋友
和同事
我想一起看
那位白发男子是谁？
新任副部长
-那家伙是老家伙-我认识他
-是Gyuri吗？-他呢？
我以为他不是化学家
打扰一下
你好
-晚上好-晚上好
我的哀悼来得如此意外
我在报纸上读过
Gyuri，你好吗？
谢谢
我已经很努力了
我正在抚养我的儿子们
这些天你做什么工作？
我是个工程师
你离开政治了吗？
非常喜欢我的工作
你为什么让他们都来？
你喜欢他们吗？
不是所有的人
他们中的几个
你也不喜欢蒂博尔
但仅自49年以来
他总是假装好像什么都没发生
虽然他知道很多事情
他将成为一名伟大的经济学家，
但他成为了党的工作人员
打扰一下，我现在必须离开你
您打算去询问每个人对Tibor的看法吗？
这是什么？
一个测试？
还是只是歇斯底里？
他们认为他是一个伟人
你确定吗？
我是
和你？
好吧，我不会让你继续前进
如果你这样说，我会送你走
你不敢
这里人太多了
而且你一直害怕丑闻
我简直不敢相信！
我已经服用了数天的镇静剂
我真的不知道该说些什么
- 求求你了，谢谢你
- 谢谢你不客气
我在罗马大使馆听到了这个消息
你的孩子，你的退休金，都还好吗？
是的，谢谢
一天晚上来看我，我想和你谈谈
好吧，我会
下个星期给我打电话
-我总是在八点钟左右进来-好吧
对不起，我必须走了
我要去法国请假
等一下
我要你来
因为我想要
蒂博尔的所有朋友在一起
互相见面
我想要
你们所有人从他的图书馆取书
随便你
请
请自便
来
来选择
妈妈这是什么
没事吧
你一定很累
别担心我不会伤到他的记忆
我为你担心
冷静
-再见-再见
再见
晚安
- 再见
再见
-再见-再见
再见我拿了这个
-给我打电话-好吧
冷静点休息一下
再见
您介意我再次致电给您吗？
我想和你谈谈，成为我的正式人
好的
没有我你还好吗
我已经十五年没见到你了
这不是真的
就在一周前
别傻了
已经十五年了
我忘了你
这是真的
因为你只是想过自己
实际上
只有头三年
-最近二十个都不错-不，那不是真的
您要求他们来是因为您需要他们的建议吗？
因为你从未爱过我
你只是怕我
你已经一个人呆了
-不好意思-不！
不要那样做你没有权利
你上演了这个小戏
美丽，悲伤
诚实的寡妇
谁有良心
你想过得好
舒适地
安详地
但是你从未实现和平
因为你内心不安
我不能为你感到抱歉
我只希望你有足够的力量
玩到最后
等待
那是István，我的儿子
你不记得我吗
不，我不
我是你父亲的朋友
伊斯特万
告诉他你为什么离开家
你没有和父亲相处
因为你一直在战斗告诉他！
妈妈冷静点这个只涉及我们两个
我不想打扰你
我现在去
再见
-再见-再见
你累了
-你最好去睡觉-不
很适合你
我非常喜欢这些，我只是不知道在哪里穿
-这个也不错-你没有我这么大的东西吗？
那边有很多东西
那里
我有一件白大衣我在巴黎买的
对我来说太大了对你来说还可以
我会试穿的
-多么好的纺织品！-太好了！
看看这些颜色！
我应该搭配哪双鞋？
是你的大小，不是吗？
-保留-不错
我什么都不想要
这些不是我的风格
丝绸！
我那里有一堆毛衣
我不能接受
那我就丢掉
哦，多么可爱！
看起来真不错！
你是这样想的吗？
亲爱的耶稣，但我要戴在哪里？
-这是迪奥（Dior），对吗？-是的
奇妙！
哦亲爱的！
所有这些漂亮的衣服！
还有书包
进来
-美好的一天-你好
-坐下-你好
我的帽子，你这个笨蛋！
要喝威士忌吗？
是的，请
卡蒂（Kati）不会进来吗？
这里发生了什么？
编辑给了我们她的衣服
我希望你让我们独自一人
我说完就去找你
我想现在和你说话
这是否意味着您要我们离开？
是的
那很好
-再见，亲爱的编辑-再见
-很久很感谢-再见
- 再见拜拜
现在，让我独自一人！
我想和你谈谈
坐下我快完成了
-下午好-你好
妈妈我在听
我下定决心不接受20万福林保险
和退休金
我让你吃
以及公寓
我今天要去卫生部签字
我要你跟我来
我不会去
我考虑周全
你有？
我不这么认为
我这没关系
无论是钱还是公寓
你父亲为此工作
-和你一起住了21年-是的
但是我们没有共同之处
除了他照顾我
我们没有离婚
他是反对它的那个人
妈妈那是你的事
但是你必须要看透
为了我父亲的记忆
一次我会真正看到一些东西
我不会和你一起去
如果您一直保持沉默直到现在，您可以继续保持沉默并忍受
你不会放弃任何事情，我不会让你
冷静
否则，你就自由了，可以随心所欲地生活
父亲总是这样说：
“你不会离婚，你可以随心所欲地生活”
我不是要冒犯您，但我不能认真考虑您的决定
如果你以前不够强壮，
您现在怎么能在租住的房间里靠1200福林住？
你没有交易
我不认为你能做到
关于道德方面，
我不会让你伤害父亲
因为，不像你，我爱他
-你不懂我-不，我不懂
-请跟我来-不，我不会
那我自己去看
卡蒂，来吧，走吧
快的
好吧，告诉她来
妈妈，你能出来吗？
晚上好
-你好-卡蒂为我们做的晚餐
她是一个很好的厨师
化妆吧妈妈
好的
干杯
相信我，我爱你，我了解你
但是现在你很紧张
我也知道
你应该去平房一个星期休息一下
我现在不能走
我有工作要做
稍微休息一下真的可以对你有好处
卡蒂会和你一起去
-照顾你-哦，是的
我有东西要安排在这里我现在不能去也不想去
好吧，那就留下来
你做你想做的
给你！
对不起，你得走了
我不知道你会来
我们最终来了
-你要待很久吗？-我还不知道
没关系
来吧，女孩们！
但是我希望你不要觉得交叉，对吗？
-好吧，再见-再见
再见，谢谢！
-谢谢，再见！-再见！
早上好
打电话给我就打开
我怎么到这里了？
昨晚我们把你带到这里伊斯特万开车，但他回去了
我在这里照顾你你需要休息
我什么都不记得了
我们在您的酒中放了安眠药
聪明的方法
巧妙地完成
您早餐想吃点什么？
咖啡？
蛋？
牛奶？
我们待一个星期
你误会了
村里有一辆公共汽车从11点出发
我乘下午火车去布达佩斯
-你做不到-我会做
我很坚强所有的门都锁好了
我到处都会跟着你
所以我必须逃跑
很搞笑
你无法逃脱
这是你的早餐
你为什么做这个？
伊斯特万问我
你爱他吗？
是的
你愿意嫁给他吗？
我会的，如果他向我求婚
我穿好衣服
过来
来
你好慈利
慈利是她的名字吗？
是的
您想午餐吃点什么？
感谢您的耐心等待，
但是就像我说的，我要带十一点钟回家
您最好不要，否则我必须将您锁定
-你会做吗？-我会
所以你会把我锁在里面
好的
既然我们要在一起度过一个星期，
我们可以一起组成这个程序
-我希望你过得愉快-你以为你是谁？
你以为我怕你吗？
你是谁？
那你跟我有什么关系
我是KatiCsák，我是化学家
我出生于45年的多罗格
我对自己不怎么想，但是
我想你怕我
因为你也怕儿子
这不是真的
我不怕他
你是
慈利！
就是这里来
好的
我希望你现在知道
我想离开就可以离开
慈利！
慈利亲爱的！
早上好
我喂她
我们住在隔壁
你是谁？
卡斯特（István）的未婚妻
我们和他妈妈一起在这里，她正在休息
哦，是的，我听说这位先生死了
-怎么编辑？-她现在睡着了
我有事要问你
你能再给狗喂一天吗？
为什么不？
-让她出去-谢谢
Cili！再见
-待会儿-非常感谢
再见
那只狗？
与邻居
很棘手
-门？-我已经锁好了
如果必须的话，你甚至会打败我
不，我就把你关起来
尝试休息，不要歇斯底里
慈利！
过来慈利
-Cili！-来吧Cili来吧
-她是你的狗吗？-不，我妈妈的
来吧慈利
她有多聪明？
-拿来-来吧，小狗！
我们要去洗个澡，Cili！
-Cili！回来吧-Cili，告诉我们你有多聪明
慈利跳！
-她不会听你的-茜莉，跳！跳！
她做到了
跳！快来吧
- 你好
这是怎么回事？
我们几乎吵架了她一定要离开
我认为我们应该停止这样做
只是继续
我们不应该放开她吗？
我们必须继续几天我知道我的母亲
她有点歇斯底里，但很快就结束了
我不这么认为
-加斯帕，把那个女孩带到这里！-给我几秒钟
哦，天哪，很冷，但是很好
禁止在这里游泳！
出来给我看你的论文！
出来！
赶快！
你在这里做什么？
-禁止在这里游泳吗？-我们在下棋
来吧快点！
出来！
狗也不喜欢
穿好衣服，快点！
赶快
你也是
-给我我的鞋子-快点
-你！穿上礼服-我？
来吧
你看起来很可爱
小心！你踩着我的衬衫！
-你要住在哪里？-在露营地
为什么？怎么了？
我知道他的问题是什么
我们有一头长发，我们是小流氓，不是吗？
来穿上
你最好表现
-我们确实表现得很好，我们只是去洗澡-我知道
-开始吧-嗨
-我不知道你在这里-洗衣服
他是我兄弟
走吧
-来吧，加斯帕-不，我要和他们一起去
也拿那个
-去警察局-我的鞋子在哪里？
加斯帕尔，回来！
来吧，Cili！
-停止回头，继续前进！-好吧
-走吧！-为什么要走？
你会在车站找到
-您也想告诉我如何呼吸吗？-我们是先锋！
午餐准备好了
你不吃饭吗
对不起
说，您可以被雇用做任何事情吗？
你想要我的儿子，你可以拥有他
我不仅要他
但他也要我
编辑亲爱的！
你好吗，玛吉特姨妈？
已经醒了吗？
是的
再会
有人告诉我你丈夫死了
让他安息
亲爱的，你还好吗？
谢谢，我很好
卡蒂（Kati）得到了钥匙
卡蒂！
打开！
再会
我儿子的未婚妻
我们已经见过面了
你什么时候要结婚？
在一年的时间里，我完成了大学
我丈夫也是10年前去世的
他是一个好人，一个好农夫
我一个人留着九个孩子
-坐下吧，玛吉特姨妈-谢谢
她是一个体面的女孩吗？
哦，是的，非常不错
那好吧
好吧，我现在要走了，我很忙
等等马吉特姨妈
我和你一起去
我去散散步
不要走
洗碗
我会很快再见
再见
我很高兴你来了
我的两个女儿将来自布达佩斯
我们在一起
我的四个儿子也经常来找我
-我们彼此依依不舍-还有金钱
还有钱
与丈夫分开的孩子们您将如何处理？
-我们给了你一个家-是的，的确是
但是我像马一样工作
-喝点酒，编辑，真的很好-谢谢
我想学习，但是没有被学校录取
我丈夫是锁匠
他是一个酒鬼，他殴打了我，所以我离开了他
你怎么现在不读书
我学习了怎么办？
妈妈会为丈夫找酒商
-你不是吗，妈妈？-我当然会
喝一杯，很好
她和玛吉特姨妈一起走了
-我们应该停止整个业务-否
反正她也不会离开
走到玛吉特姨妈那里，我待会儿来
好的
进来
你爱我吗？
我愿意
我想
还有更多
你现在一定很伤心
你为什么难过？
她的丈夫一周前去世了
你爱他吗？
她做过
他是布达佩斯的大个子
如果你爱他，喝一杯
如果你没有也一样
在天堂里闪闪发亮，闪闪发光，闪闪发光！
指引可怜的小伙子
因为他找不到情人的房子
是我求爱的美女
对于丑陋的人，我没有注意
哦，我的心，没人知道
我爱那个金发女郎
只有吉普赛人在玩violink才知道
编辑，你的歌是什么？
“路很宽”
一条路这么宽，一条路那么长
我的天使出发了
我的天使，从漫长的旅程中回来
记住你的诺言
我们不能从漫长的旅程中回来
没有隐藏的爱
我的爱比大海还大
我比枯叶寂寞
-你好，我的儿子-祝你有美好的一天
这是我的葡萄酒商
-美好的一天，玛吉特姨妈-美好的一天
有一些菜炖牛肉，编辑，真的很好
我知道你会跟着我
继续喝一杯
不要再喝了
我们回家吧
我今天要回布达佩斯
你喝醉了回家睡觉
那怎么了！我喝醉了
不要再喝了
不要喝
我不会去，别管我
喝一杯，你太平淡了
我不会去任何地方！
我回去吧，我会做我想做的
-帮帮我，好吗？让我们来编辑家-好吧
在哪里？
你要带她去哪
不要带她走！
-走吧，好吗？-否
-走吧-不
我们不要做一个场景
我不会去
你为什么不让我一个人呢？玛吉特，帮帮我
不要让她带我走
-冷静点，亲爱的编辑-否
你的悲伤很快就会过去
求求你，不要让她把我带走！
你会睡一会，它会过去
-不想让我一个人-跟我们来
-拜托，别管我-走吧
我找到了这个
来喝一杯
不要喝
来吧
好的
来喝一杯
你真是个体面的宪兵
不
你毕竟不那么体面
你以为我是胆小鬼
那就是我
我忍受了我的丈夫，我没有离婚，
我没有勇气去做
但
至少我知道
我知道我是什么样
但是你以为你在对我做什么
有所不同
你只想嫁给István，
因为你和他一起睡
因为他很聪明
又帅
但我知道
我儿子就像他父亲一样
请不要再喝了
请别打扰我！
走吧，让我一个人！
我会离开你一个人，但首先我想告诉你一些事情
你说我是宪兵，平淡无奇
我这样做是因为我不了解您发生了什么事
而且因为我和你儿子睡过
好吧，也许我确实很平淡
并没有什么复杂的感觉，
但是，我知道我自己，我认识你
你绝对是一个胆小鬼，你从未冒险
拥有高级公寓和别墅没有错
我也要
你为什么说每个人都尊重你的丈夫？
你知道这已经很久了
人们认为他自私，自负和保守
你知道的，仍然忍受着，更糟的是，你为他服务
现在，如果您想扮演寡妇的角色，
我让你走
这个玩宪兵的事情对我来说真是愚蠢
你做你想做的
除了你是对的
你儿子又帅又聪明
这就是为什么我爱他
但是现在我去
卡蒂！
卡蒂！停！
我想跟你说话！
卡蒂！
你为什么要离开？
-留在这里-不
我要去
留在这儿
我需要你
我爱你
你不需要我我告诉过你，我不会做
一个人做
-你考虑透了吗？-我做到了
留在这儿
留在这里明白吗？
我要你留下，我要！
我已经告诉过你，我不会留下，我要走了
你好，加斯帕尔！
你在这里做什么？
只是和女孩消磨时间
你离开他们了吗？
是的，我要回布达佩斯
好吧再见我待会儿
好的再见
她穿着一件白色的毛衣她不哀悼
你包里有什么？
别管那个女孩！
让我向她求婚！
别管她了！别再烦了！
让她走！
我们向您告别
再见！
嘿，看看谁在那里！
链条，链条，转弯链条，
车削链的线，是否会是线
谁敢否认我们需要
谁敢否认我们需要这种光？
当我终于放开她时去看她的脸
结束